theeuropeansummit.com 2019-05-26

# Privacy - TES Affiliate Conferences

EUROPEAN EVENT MANAGEMENT S.R.O. PRIVACY POLICY  
In protecting your privacy we are providing this statement detailing our online data practices and the options you have about the way your personal data is collected and used on these websites. The following information provides an overview of how we process your personal data and your rights under data protection law and provide all other relevant information according to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Who is data controller and who can I contact in this regard?  
Our company, i.e. European Event Management s.r.o., with its registered office at Odborů 289/10, Nové Město, 120 00 Prague 2, the Czech Republic, Identification No. 04749570, is the data controller of your data and is, therefore, responsible for the data processing. If you have any questions or concerns about the processing of your personal data by our company you may contact us at sales@europeaneventmanagementsa.com.

What sources and data do we use and what personal data do we process?  
We process personal data which we receive from you on these websites [www.theeuropeansummit.com](http://www.theeuropeansummit.com/) in the context of our business relationship. In certain cases, we may also process personal data from publicly available sources (e. g., commercial registers and registers of associations, press, media, Internet, social media) which we lawfully obtain and are permitted to process.

The data which we process include all identification data of participants of our conferences (e.g. name, e-mail, company name, address, mobile, industry sector), other information which relates to the participation on our conferences/summits (e.g. summit name, payment amount, information about payment, company’s details), optionally also interests of the participants and certain answers to our questions provided during registration.

Why do we process your data (purpose) and on what legal basis?  
We process the aforementioned personal data in compliance with the provisions of GDPR for the following purposes:

  * for the performance of contractual obligations (article 6 (1) b) GDPR)

We use your personal data to complete your requests for our programs and services, to address your inquiries about our programs. We sometimes use this data to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests, to fulfil a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your business with us.

  * for the purposes of our legitimate interests (article 6 (1) f) GDPR)

Where allowed and necessary, we process your data above and beyond the actual performance of our contractual obligations based on our legitimate interests that lies above all in direct marketing and that we may offer you other products, programs or services that might be of interest to you. For this purpose, we may combine data we acquire online with other records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, please email to submit your request. Our company’s websites covered by this Privacy Policy will not use or distribute your personal data in ways without also providing you with an opportunity to opt-out of these uses.

Who receives my data?  
Within and outside our company those recipients are given access to your data which require them in order to perform our contractual obligations. Outside our company it maybe companies and/or recipients who are helping us organize each particular conference/summit. Access to your personal data is provided also to our hosting providers (currently Mojohost BV). Your personal data is further provided to Wirecard Bank AG which takes care about the payments on our websites, provides other relevant payments services and processes your personal data as a data controller (for more information see [https://www.wirecardbank.de/DSGVO](https://login.mailingwork.de/-link2/13528/397/19/69/1547/xn6iXMU1/dDAT5unCj0/0)).

We may disclose your data in response to legal obligations, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such data in response to a law enforcement agency's request. Agents and contractors of our company who have access to your personal data are required to protect this data in a way that is consistent with this Privacy Policy, for example, not using the data for any purpose other than to complete the services they are handling for our company.

Your data may not be transferred outside the EU or the EEA countries (although they may be processed also outside these countries, especially when the conferences are being held outside these countries).

Please also note that collection of your data by Strategic Partner Sites and Sponsors Links on our websites may direct you to other websites and their information policies and privacy guidelines may differ from ours. Please read the privacy statements on other websites as we have no control over what these strategic partner websites do with your data collected and/or submitted. Our company’s websites covered by this Privacy Policy sometimes may offer programs (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that are sponsored by or co-branded with identified strategic partners. The strategic partners may obtain your personal data that you voluntarily submit to participate in the programs. Our company has no control over these strategic partners' use of this data.

How long will my data be stored?  
We process and store your personal data as long as it is necessary for the performance of our contractual obligations. If the data are no longer required for the performance of our contractual obligations, they are regularly deleted, unless the further processing (for a limited time) is necessary for the following purposes:

  * Compliance with records retention periods according to relevant legal rules.
  * Preservation of evidence within the scope of statutes of limitations.

Do we process cookies and what are cookies, what are non-user data?  
To better understand our site traffic, many of our Internet pages use "cookies" to track user experience. Cookies are text files placed in your computer's browser. Cookies do not tell us your e-mail address or other unique user specific data unless you choose to provide this data to us by, for example, registering at one of our websites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with unique user specific data, this data may be built into the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and programs on our websites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site) or to save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you programs, services or products.

Please also note that non-unique user data may be collected when you visit many of our site pages such as the kind of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox), the kind of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 2000 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, MSN). Such data are, however, not considered as personal data as we may not identify you. We sometimes use the non-unique user specific data that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your online activities. We also may use this data to analyse site usage, as well as to offer you programs, services or products.

Are my personal data protected?  
We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect and help prevent unauthorized access, control data security, and properly use the data collected online.

What data protection rights do I have?  
Our company allows you to exercise all rights you have according to GDPR, if the conditions for their application are fulfilled. Please note that every data subject, including you, has a right of access (article 15 GDPR), a right to rectification (article 16 GDPR), a right to erasure (article 17 GDPR), a right to restriction of processing (article 18 GDPR), a right to object (article 21 GDPR) and a right to data portability (article 20 GDPR). Please note that we do not make decisions based solely on automated processing (article 22 GDPR).

Data subjects also have a right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority (article 77 GDPR). The list of appropriate supervisory authorities for each country can be found here: <http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080>

For instructions on how you can access the unique user specific data that this European Event Management site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such data, please contact us at sales@europeaneventmanagementsa.com. Please note that to protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Right to object (article 21 GDPR)  
Under the conditions laid down by GDPR, you have the right to object. If you lodge an objection, we will no longer process your personal data unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms or unless the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.

In certain cases, we process your personal data for direct marketing purposes. You have the right to object at any time to such processing of your personal data. In that case, we will no longer process your personal data for such purposes.
